<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<odoo>
    <template id="theme_softhealer_store_terms_and_conditions_banner_snippet_template" name="Banner">
        <!--banner
        start-->
        <section id="sh_terms_condition_banner"
            class="sh_softhealer_store_terms_condition_banner sh_other_page_banner">
            <div class="container">
                <div class="sh_banner_content">
                    <h2 class="sh_banner_title">Terms and Conditions</h2>
                    <ul class="sh_banner_breadcrumb">
                        <li>
                            <a class="sh_banner_breadcrumb_link" href="/">Home <span
                                    class="sh_banner_breadcrumb_icon fa fa-angle-right"></span>
                            </a>
                        </li>
                        <li>
                            <span class="sh_banner_normal_text">Terms and Conditions</span>
                        </li>
                    </ul>
					<p class="sh_banner_date">
                        Please read these Terms and Conditions ("Agreement") carefully before using
                        or purchasing
                        any software from our store. This Agreement sets forth the legally binding
                        terms and
                        conditions for the sale of software by our company to you, the customer.</p>
                </div>
            </div>
        </section>
        <!--banner
        end-->
    </template>
    <template id="theme_softhealer_store_terms_and_conditions_rules_snippet_template" name="Rules">
        <section class="sh_softhealer_store_terms_condition" id="sh_softhealer_store_terms_condition">
							<div class="container">
								<div class="sh_terms_condition">
									<div class="row sh_content_box">
									<div class="col-xxl-10 col-xl-10 col-lg-10 col-md-12 mx-auto d-block">
										<h2 class="sh_sub_heading">1. Acceptance of Terms and Conditions</h2>		
										<p class="sh_text">
											By accessing our website or purchasing software from our company, you acknowledge and
											agree to be bound by the terms and conditions outlined in this Agreement. If you do not
											agree with these terms, you should not use our website or purchase any software from us.
										</p>

										<h2 class="sh_sub_heading">2. Software License</h2>		
										<div class="sh_text">
											<div class="sh_icon"><span class="fa fa-circle"></span></div><div class="sh_desc"><span class="sub_title">Ownership : </span> All software purchased from softhealer is licensed, not sold. We retain full
											ownership and intellectual property rights to the software.</div>
										</div>
										<div class="sh_text">
											<div class="sh_icon"><span class="fa fa-circle"></span></div><div class="sh_desc"><span class="sub_title"> License Grant : </span> We grant you a non-exclusive, non-transferable license to use the
												software for your personal or business use, as specified in the software's documentation or
												license agreement.</div>
										</div>
										<div class="sh_text">
											<div class="sh_icon"><span class="fa fa-circle"></span></div><div class="sh_desc"><span class="sub_title"> Restrictions : </span>  We grant you a non-exclusive, non-transferable license to use the
												software for your personal or business use, as specified in the software's documentation or
												license agreement.</div>
										</div>
										<h2 class="sh_sub_heading">3. Ordering and Payment</h2>		
										<div class="sh_text">
											<div class="sh_icon"><span class="fa fa-circle"></span></div><div class="sh_desc"><span class="sub_title">Orders : </span> All orders for software are subject to acceptance by softhealer. We reserve the
											right to refuse or cancel any order at our discretion.</div>
										</div>
										<div class="sh_text">
											<div class="sh_icon"><span class="fa fa-circle"></span></div><div class="sh_desc"><span class="sub_title"> Pricing : </span> The prices for software are as stated on our website at the time of purchase.
												We reserve the right to change the prices without prior notice.</div>
										</div>
										<div class="sh_text">
											<div class="sh_icon"><span class="fa fa-circle"></span></div><div class="sh_desc"><span class="sub_title"> Payment : </span>  You agree to pay the full amount for the software at the time of purchase.
												Payment can be made through the available payment methods specified on our website.</div>
										</div>
										<h2 class="sh_sub_heading">4. Delivery and Support</h2>		
										<div class="sh_text">
											<div class="sh_icon"><span class="fa fa-circle"></span></div><div class="sh_desc"><span class="sub_title"> Delivery : </span> Upon successful payment, we will provide you with the necessary instructions
												and access credentials to download and install the software.</div>
										</div>
										<div class="sh_text">
											<div class="sh_icon"><span class="fa fa-circle"></span></div><div class="sh_desc"><span class="sub_title"> Support : </span> We will provide technical support and assistance in accordance with the terms
											specified in the software's documentation or support agreement. Any additional support
											services may be subject to additional charges.</div>
										</div>
										<h2 class="sh_sub_heading">5. Refunds</h2>		
										<div class="sh_text">
											<div class="sh_icon"><span class="fa fa-circle"></span></div><div class="sh_desc"><span class="sub_title"> Refunds : </span> We offer refunds in accordance with the softhealer refund policy, which is
											available on our website. Please review the policy carefully before making a purchase.
											To know more <a href="#">Follow this link</a></div>
										</div>
										<h2 class="sh_sub_heading">6. Limitation of Liability</h2>		
										<div class="sh_text">
											<div class="sh_icon"><span class="fa fa-circle"></span></div><div class="sh_desc">To the maximum extent permitted by law, softhealer shall not be liable for any direct, indirect,
											incidental, consequential, or special damages arising out of or in connection with the use or
											inability to use the software, even if advised of the possibility of such damages.</div>
										</div>
										<h2 class="sh_sub_heading">7. Governing Law and Jurisdiction</h2>		
										<div class="sh_text">
											<div class="sh_icon"><span class="fa fa-circle"></span></div><div class="sh_desc">By accessing and using <a href="https://store.softhealer.com/">https://store.softhealer.com/ </a>, you acknowledge and agree that any disputes arising between you and Softhealer Technologies Pvt Ltd shall be governed by the laws of India.</div>
										</div>
										<h2 class="sh_sub_heading">8. Modifications to the Agreement</h2>		
										<div class="sh_text">
											<div class="sh_icon"><span class="fa fa-circle"></span></div><div class="sh_desc">We reserve the right to modify or update this Agreement at any time without prior notice. Any
											changes will be effective immediately upon posting on our website. Your continued use of
											our website or purchase of a software after any modifications constitutes your acceptance of
											the revised terms.</div>
										</div>
										<h2 class="sh_sub_heading">9. Entire Agreement</h2>		
										<div class="sh_text">
											<div class="sh_icon"><span class="fa fa-circle"></span></div><div class="sh_desc">This Agreement constitutes the entire agreement between you and softhealer regarding the
												sale of software and supersedes any prior agreements or understandings, whether written or
												oral.</div>
										</div>
										<div class="sh_text">
											<div class="sh_icon"><span class="fa fa-circle"></span></div><div class="sh_desc">By using our website or purchasing software from softhealer, you acknowledge that you
											have read, understood, and agreed to these Terms and Conditions. Please contact our
											customer support for clarification if you have any questions or concerns.</div>
										</div>
									</div>
									</div>
									<div class="row sh_content_box">
										
										<div class="col-xxl-10 col-xl-10 col-lg-10 col-md-12 mx-auto d-block mt-5">
										<h2 class="sh_title_heading">Return and Refund Policies</h2>
										<p class="sh_text">
											We understand the importance of transparency and clear communication when it comes to
											our return and refund policies for software services. As a provider of software services, we
											would like to emphasize that software purchases are considered final and non-refundable.
										</p>
										<h2 class="sh_sub_heading">1. Pre-Purchase Evaluation and Demos</h2>		
										<p class="sh_text">
											We understand that selecting the right software service is crucial for your business. To make it easier in the decision-making process, we provide detailed product information and demonstration URLs when available. We encourage potential customers to take advantage of these resources to evaluate the software service and determine if it aligns with their requirements before making a purchase.
										</p>
										<h2 class="sh_sub_heading">2. Technical Errors and Unresolved Bugs</h2>		
										<p class="sh_text">
											If you encounter critical technical errors or persistent bugs within the software service that
											our support team is unable to resolve, we will consider providing a refund. It is important to
											note that this applies solely to issues stemming from the core functionality of the software
											service itself. Refunds will not be granted for errors or conflicts arising from third-party
											applications or custom modifications made by the customer.
										</p>
										<h2 class="sh_sub_heading">3. Collaboration for Issue Resolution</h2>		
										<p class="sh_text mb-4">
											In order to effectively address issues, bugs, and errors, we require the cooperation and
											assistance of our customers. When reporting any technical problems, customers are
											requested to provide access to their server details, GitHub repository, or any other relevant
											sources where our software has been installed. This access is crucial for our technical teams
											to investigate, reproduce, and troubleshoot the reported issues effectively.
										</p>
										<p class="sh_text mb-4">
											By granting access to the necessary resources, customers enable our teams to delve into
											the specific environment where the software is deployed. This collaborative approach
											ensures a more accurate assessment of the reported issues and facilitates efficient
											resolution.
										</p>
										<p class="sh_text mb-4">
											We understand the importance of safeguarding customer data and sensitive information.
											Rest assured, any access provided will be treated with the utmost confidentiality and used
											solely for the purpose of resolving the reported issues. Our teams strictly adhere to data
											privacy and security protocols to ensure the protection of customer information.
										</p>
										<p class="sh_text mb-4">
											We appreciate your understanding and willingness to collaborate during the issue-resolution
											process. Your cooperation enables us to deliver effective solutions and enhance the overall
											performance and reliability of our software services.
										</p>
										<p class="sh_text mb-4">
											If you have any concerns or require further clarification regarding the collaboration process,
											please do not hesitate to contact our support team. We are here to assist you throughout the
											troubleshooting and resolution process.
										</p>
										<h2 class="sh_sub_heading">4. Failure to Deliver Advertised Features</h2>		
										<p class="sh_text">
											We strive to ensure that our software services deliver all the advertised features and
											functionalities. In the rare event that we are unable to provide a significant feature or
											functionality as described in our product documentation and marketing materials, a refund
											may be considered. Please note that minor variances, improvements, or changes in the
											software service that do not significantly impact its core functionality may not be eligible for a
											refund.
										</p>
										<h2 class="sh_sub_heading">5. Refund Eligibility Timeframe</h2>		
										<p class="sh_text">
											To be eligible for a refund, a request must be made within 60 days from the date of
											purchase. After this period, refund requests may not be considered. We encourage
											customers to thoroughly evaluate the software service and report any issues or concerns
											promptly to our support team.
										</p>
										<h2 class="sh_sub_heading">6. Support and Resolution</h2>		
										<p class="sh_text mb-4">
											While refunds are not our primary approach, we prioritize customer satisfaction and aim to provide exceptional support. Our support team is readily available to assist you with any challenges you may face while using our software service. We encourage you to reach out to our support team for prompt assistance and guidance in resolving any issues you encounter.

										</p>
										<p class="sh_text o_default_snippet_text">
											We appreciate your understanding of our refund policy, which is designed to ensure fairness
											and maintain the highest level of quality in our software services. We continuously strive to
											deliver reliable and feature-rich solutions to meet your business needs. Should you have any
											further questions or concerns regarding our refund policy, please do not hesitate to contact
											our customer support team for clarification and assistance.											
										</p>
										<h2 class="sh_sub_heading o_default_snippet_text">7. Exceptional Customer Support</h2>		
										<p class="sh_text o_default_snippet_text">
											While we do not offer refunds or returns for purchased software services, we are committed
											to providing exceptional customer support. Our dedicated support team is available to
											address any issues, provide guidance, and assist with troubleshooting. If you encounter any
											difficulties or have questions regarding the software service, please reach out to our support
											team, and we will be glad to assist you.
										</p>
										</div>
									</div>
								</div>
							</div>
						</section>
    </template>
</odoo>