<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<odoo>

    <!-- Privacy Policy Page -->
    <record id="theme_softhealer_website_privacy_policy_page" model="website.page">
		<field name="name">Privacy Policy</field>
		<field name="url">/privacy-policy</field>
		<field name="website_published">True</field>
		<field name="type">qweb</field>
		<field name="key">theme_softhealer_website.theme_softhealer_website_privacy_policy_template</field>
		<field name="arch" type="xml">
			<t name="Privacy Policy Template"
         t-name="theme_softhealer_website.theme_softhealer_website_privacy_policy_template">
				<t t-call="website.layout">
					<div class="oe_structure oe_empty" id="wrap">
                        <!--  start banner Privacy Policy section  -->
                        <section id="sh_privacy_policy_banner"
                            class="sh_privacy_policy_banner sh_other_page_banner">
                            <div class="sh_banner_content">
                                <h2 class="sh_banner_title">Privacy Policy</h2>
                                <p class="sh_banner_text">We makes your business easy</p>
                                <ul class="sh_banner_breadcrumb">
                                    <li>
                                        <a class="sh_banner_breadcrumb_link" href="/">Home<span
                                                class="sh_banner_breadcrumb_icon fa fa-angle-right"></span></a>
                                    </li>
                                    <li>
                                        <span class="sh_banner_normal_text">Privacy Policy</span>
                                    </li>
                                </ul>
                            </div>
                        </section>
                        <!--  end banner Privacy Policy section  -->
                        <section id="sh_privacy_policy_rules" class="sh_privacy_policy_rules ">
                            <div class="container">
                                <div class="sh_privacy_policy_content">
                                    <div class="row">
                                        <div class="col-lg-10 offset-lg-1">
                                            <p class="sh_text">
                                                <b>
                                                    <font class="sh_heading_title">About Privacy Policy:</font>
                                                </b>
                                                <font>We are a leading ERP solution provider catering to businesses of all sizes. Our comprehensive
                                                    ERP solutions are designed to streamline operations, optimize processes, and enhance
                                                    productivity across various industries. This page is intended to inform visitors about our policies
                                                    regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of personal information for users of our service. We
                                                    are committed to protecting the privacy and confidentiality of our user's personal information
                                                    and have implemented measures to ensure its secure handling.</font>
                                                <br />
                                                <br />
                                                <font>
                                                    By using our service, you agree to the collection and use of information in
                                                    accordance with this policy. The "Personal Information" collected is used for
                                                    providing and improving the service, and will not be shared with anyone except
                                                    as described in this "Privacy Policy".
                                                </font>
                                                <br />
                                                <br />
                                                <font>
                                                    The terms used in this "Privacy Policy" have the same meanings as in our "Terms
                                                    and Conditions", which can be found on the ERP app unless otherwise defined in
                                                    this "Privacy Policy".
                                                </font>


                                            </p>
                                            <p class="sh_text">
                                                <b>
                                                    <font class="sh_heading_title">Information Collection and Use:</font>
                                                </b>
                                                <font>While using our service, we may require you to
                                                    provide us with certain personally identifiable information to enhance your
                                                    experience. The information we request will be retained by us and used as
                                                    described in this privacy policy.
                                                </font>
                                            </p>
                                            <p class="sh_text">
                                                <b>
                                                    <font class="sh_heading_title">Log Data:</font>
                                                </b>
                                                <font>We collect data and information (through third party products) on your
                                                    phone called "Log Data" whenever you use our service. This "Log Data" may
                                                    include information such as your device Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, device
                                                    name, operating system version, the configuration of the app when utilizing our
                                                    service, the time and date of your use of the service, and other statistics.</font>
                                            </p>
                                            <p class="sh_text">
                                                <span class="sh_heading_title">
                                                    Cookies:</span>
                                                <font>Cookies are files with a small amount of data commonly used as
                                                    anonymous unique identifiers. These are sent to your browser from the websites
                                                    you visit and stored on your device's internal memory. While this service does
                                                    not use these “cookies” explicitly, the app may use third party code and libraries
                                                    that use “cookies” to collect information and improve their services. You have
                                                    the option to either accept or refuse these cookies, and you may not be able to
                                                    use some portions of this service if you choose to refuse our cookies.</font>
                                            </p>
                                            <p class="sh_text">
                                                <b>
                                                    <font class="sh_heading_title">Service Providers:</font>
                                                </b>
                                                <font>
                                                    We may employ third-party companies and individuals for a
                                                    variety of reasons, such as to facilitate our service, to provide the service on our
                                                    behalf, to perform service-related services, or to assist us in analyzing how our
                                                    service is used. We want to inform users that these third parties have access to
                                                    your "Personal Information" only to perform the tasks assigned to them on our
                                                    behalf. However, they are obligated not to disclose or use the information for any
                                                    other purpose.
                                                </font>
                                            </p>
                                            <p class="sh_text">
                                                <b>
                                                    <font class="sh_heading_title">Security:</font>
                                                </b>
                                                <font>We take the protection of your Personal Information seriously and use
                                                    commercially acceptable means to safeguard it. However, please keep in mind
                                                    that no method of transmission over the internet, or method of electronic
                                                    storage is 100% secure and reliable, and we cannot guarantee its absolute
                                                    security.
                                                    </font>
                                            </p>
                                            <p class="sh_text">
                                                <b>
                                                    <font class="sh_heading_title">Links to Other Sites:</font>
                                                </b>
                                                <font>This service may contain links to other sites. If you click on
                                                    a third-party link, you will be directed to that site. Please note that these
                                                    external sites are not operated by us. Therefore, we strongly advise you to review
                                                    the Privacy Policy of these websites. We have no control over and assume no
                                                    responsibility for the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third-party
                                                    sites or services.</font>
                                            </p>
                                            <p class="sh_text">
                                                <b>
                                                    <font class="sh_heading_title">Children’s Privacy:</font>
                                                </b>
                                                <font>Our services are not directed to anyone under the age of 13.
                                                    We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children
                                                    under 13. If we become aware that a child under 13 has provided us with personal
                                                    information, we immediately delete this from our servers. If you are a parent or
                                                    guardian and you are aware that your child has provided us with personal
                                                    information, please contact us so that we will be able to take the necessary
                                                    actions.</font>
                                            </p>
                                            <p class="sh_text">
                                                <b>
                                                    <font class="sh_heading_title">Changes to This Privacy Policy:</font>
                                                </b>
                                                <font>We may update our "Privacy Policy" from time to
                                                    time. Thus, we advise you to review this page periodically for any changes. We
                                                    will notify you of any changes by posting the new "Privacy Policy" on this page.
                                                    This policy is effective as.</font>
                                            </p>
                                            <p class="sh_text">
                                                <b>
                                                    <font class="sh_heading_title">Contact Us:</font>
                                                </b>
                                                <font>If you have any questions or suggestions about our
                                                    "Privacy Policy", do not hesitate to contact us at
                                                    info@softhealer.com<br/></font>
                                            </p>
                                        </div>
                                    </div>
                                </div>
                            </div>
                        </section>
                    </div>
                </t>
            </t>
        </field>
    </record>

</odoo>